{
    "id": "8c2b31b1e5814a9bb9f45e590cbd5cdc",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "There is too ………………….noise in the street.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "many"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e240ab1a3c1047a4ac235619ac16520c"
        },
        {
            "question": "How ………………….. people do you want to help you?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "many"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e36a35fc588a4897bf1a5b390d8b8c24"
        },
        {
            "question": "They do …………………. a lot of business in the Middle East.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "very",
                "quite"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "36efc16f8a26402c80dd7437b0e75755"
        },
        {
            "question": "He speaks ………………… a few languages.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "very",
                "quite",
                "rather"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "25acf79b00cd418ab56ae04c22816189"
        },
        {
            "question": "There are …………………. too many weapons in the world.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "far",
                "quite",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f3ece1fda76a4eb58e26db3303bdd19d"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… of philosophy is concerned with questions nobody can answer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Much",
                "Many"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "92f521464b3740e19a88aec37d24fbbf"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. of the city was without electricity last night.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Most",
                "Much"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "896f8b5b54004a3b9cb8648744206b4b"
        },
        {
            "question": "We have bought too …………………. butter.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "many"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dfe623882f284dc5b7f97fe23980ee47"
        },
        {
            "question": "I think you have made …………………. a lot of mistakes.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "far",
                "very",
                "rather"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "87073080d5b546218ae5b1638cee9de1"
        },
        {
            "question": "This weather …………………. gets on my nerves.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "kind of",
                "kinds of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "43edff3b08164e3c81784fac07b31ea8"
        }
    ]
}